Day 2 of the class trip is about chillin' with your snowmies.
Everything is so beautiful this time of year.
Yeah, the leaves were pretty enough.
Shame about this timing, though.
Timing? For what?
Oh, don't play dumb with me.
We're going to the same places as him, right?
Oh, probably not. That was more like a maybe-we'll-see-each-other kind of situation.
Getting to snap some cool photos out here is enough to make me happy.
Though honestly, seeing him would've been nice.
You should've made plans. You have to pick a time and a place to hang out.
Don't sit around hoping you'll happen to run into him.
What? Planning to see him outside of school alone?
There's no way I could do that.
Maybe, but that would mean I'd have to leave you by yourself.
Hm? Wait, for real? That's your reason?
Are you my mom now?
I'm sorry, I'm just fishing for excuses.
You're forgiven.
But you know I can't stand when people tiptoe around the truth.
I know, and I'm sorry.
Hey, what are you ladies talking about?
Nothing much. What happened to the truth?
WithQuény for men
眼鏡を外してさ
ちゃんと目を合わせてよ
カメラのシャッターを切って
恋を閉じ込めてよ
Thank you.
Seriously?
Who would be cringe enough to actually do it?
Make way!
I'll do it!
Well...
Whoa, he might actually get there.
Right!
Left!
Light!
Wait, which one?
Hello, handsome.
Congrats on finding true love.
Norimo!
What is wrong with you, man?
You're gonna kill my chances!
Au contraire.
I'm as big as five stones put together.
You got five times the game.
You just made that up.
Hey, check it out.
I guess great minds think alike.
Huh?
Isn't that group seven?
Say hi to him.
Oh no, he's enjoying time with his friends.
I don't wanna butt in and make things awkward.
Hmm.
Well, if you really don't wanna talk to him, then I'm not gonna force you to.
Okay, over here, lovebirds!
Hey, Tani, smile!
Smile, you know, like a person?
Come on!
Over this way!
Smile for Mr. Plushy!
We're in high school, dude.
Suzuki, relax your smile!
You're doing that thing with your face!
Hey, what does that mean?
Please just take it.
Ah!
Oh!
Oh, um, I'm sorry for the intrusion.
Hope I'm not a bother.
I just saw you, and so I thought I'd try and say hello.
Dude, back off!
Hey, it's the Nishter! Get in the selfie, girl!
At least the view is nice.
Where did that come from?
Yamada sent the pictures from earlier.
Oh, wow. What a colorful assortment of weirdos.
It's crazy.
The class trip has got everyone in a good mood, including me.
Yeah, but you missed your chance to take a photo with just you and him.
Could we take one with just us two?
I couldn't do that with all those people standing around.
But I did say hi. That was enough to drain my emotional fuel tank.
Oh, for sure. You gave it your all.
And then there's Yamada, who's texting both of us these photos.
He should have just texted Nishter privately.
Completely clueless.
He blew a golden opportunity.
Huh? He texted again.
Maybe another pic?
What did he send?
I guess that he wants to meet me.
But right now? Right now, right now?
What am I going to do?
You'll figure it out. Go.
What?
But Owen, I can't leave you all alone.
I have an important live stream to watch, and I cannot be disturbed.
Go.
Oh, okay.
Yo, wait up.
I wasn't expecting so many people to be wandering around the hotel.
There he is.
Looks like other girls are chatting with him.
Wait.
Am I not the only one he texted about meeting up tonight?
I guess it's possible.
Oh, they're leaving.
I know someone else is coming.
I thought people only greeted each other like that on TV.
Come to think of it, Yamada does hang out with girls pretty often.
Uh-oh.
All this time, Yamada has been really friendly to me,
and I've been taking it as a sign that he likes me.
It turns my brain into goop every time.
But wait.
What if this is all an embarrassing misunderstanding on my part?
Like this is something that never happens to me,
but for Yamada, it's just another day.
What do I do?
I'm so inexperienced,
I never thought to take a step back and question it all.
Hey.
How come you didn't say hi?
Oh.
You were busy with other people earlier.
Then more people after that.
Ah.
Didn't want anybody to see us?
Maybe.
This is bad.
I'm getting all subconscious.
Yeah, I totally feel ya.
It's too crowded here.
Hmm.
Come on.
Let's go find a spot to chat by ourselves.
All the paranoid theories that were running wild in my mind just melted away in a second.
Yamada's words and actions are always so straightforward.
He says what he means.
Oh, did you see this cat over by Kinkaku-ji?
Oh, I didn't.
It's so cute.
Here's Taira.
That guy I told you about.
Oh, I think I've seen him around before.
And this is Azuma.
She's very pretty.
The big guy's Morimo.
Morimo?
Oh, bath time.
I should probably sit back.
Yeah, I should too.
Nishi?
Huh?
Do you want to hang out later?
Like after the class trip?
Huh?
I just really want to take you somewhere quiet and chill.
Anywhere you want.
What do you say?
Okay.
What should I do?
Oh.
There's so much I don't understand about the way Yamada feels and acts, but...
You know I can't stand when people tiptoe around the truth.
I need to be honest with myself.
I can't push my feelings down anymore.
I like him.
Nothing beats bed rot.
Back in middle school, I was too lame to say I didn't want to go on my class trip.
So along I went, counting down the hours until it ended and I could go home.
But nah, it's different.
Surprising as it may seem, I'm having fun.
A lot of fun.
Freeze the day on day three!
Time for class activities.
Teacher!
My stomach wants ice cream!
Seriously?
Huh?
Yeah, go ahead.
You're cool with that?
Oh yeah, I mean, we're pretty ahead of schedule.
Oh, hundo pee!
We're breezing past the other classes.
Eat our dust!
As long as you make it back to the bus before it leaves, feel free to run off wherever.
Yeah!
All right!
What's funny?
Nothing.
Stop looking at me like that.
Huh.
After breaking free of the past, there have been times where I almost let my excitement show.
And when I sense that it's about to escape, I push it back down.
Especially when I'm with Azuma.
It's the perfect recipe for...
Crippling self-consciousness and self-loathing.
Whoa.
Where'd that come from?
Ooh!
Wait a sec!
I'm gonna buy some deal tweets first!
It looks like there's enough to share.
Cutie!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, Tida, wanna go halfsies on a pack with me?
I have fun.
Whoa!
Why are they super bottles?
How do you not feed those mugs?
What are the time, besties?
Ow!
Eat the cracker, not my hand!
Gah!
Ear spit!
Simmer down, guys.
Hey, you got one earlier!
No seconds, bro!
Stop it!
Yamada's a real deer whisperer, ain't he?
You guys!
The deer ate all my treats and then they just left like it meant nothing!
Hey!
Tida's empty-handed and they still love him.
Oh, Alexei!
You fucking Casanova!
Stop laughing and help me get out of here!
Huh?
Hello!
If we could have your attention up here, please!
It's time for an important PSA!
We're turning this sucker into a party blast!
So if you're ready to arrange, say yeah!
Yeah!
We are not at a concert, sit down!
Shout out to my guy, Tani, in the front row!
He is parsec!
MC, more like TMI.
Tida!
Huh?
Over here!
You know what I think it's time for?
Let's play a little riddle game!
Question number one!
Okay, people!
Does anybody know what you've got to do with the snacks I bought today?
Alright, pee our teeth?
Those kind of remind me of our trip in elementary school.
Time flies.
Nabe recommended them.
You got some kind of problem with the nabe, sweet tooth?
Turn back around before we hit a bump.
Ooh, roulette!
You never know if it's sour or sweet.
You can have it.
Just tell me what you get.
Here.
I don't get it.
Boy, it's a pine, you bird brain.
Oh.
It's sour.
I'm not even phased.
I said it's sour.
What do you want from me?
What does a helpful bird do when there's a problem?
Oh?
Back here!
Oh!
An active participant!
Hit me, Zuma girl!
They squawk it out?
And...
Incorrect!
Wow, she got it wrong.
Oh, really?
I so thought I nailed that one.
I did it.
And what's that look?
You disappointed in me?
What?
No, dude.
It's just...
Was Zuma always like this?
Oh, Tani.
You okay, man?
You don't want to miss dinner, my dude!
All you can eat, eat, eat, me, me, me!
Don't talk about food right now, dude.
Go on without me.
I just want some fresh air.
R.I.P. bro.
If you have trouble finding us, call me.
Thank you.
Lame?
Of course this is the one time I ran out of tea.
That's all right.
Thank you.
Wow, soda before a buffet?
Chill out.
It's just me.
It's not for me.
I read somewhere online soda can help settle an upset stomach.
Okay, now it's your turn to chill out.
Do you usually get carsick on longer trips like that?
I don't.
I'm normally just fine.
That was weird.
But I do feel better now.
That's such a relief.
Though maybe you weren't feeling good in the first place, and we still have one more day left.
I'll be fine.
Good.
It's gonna get chilly soon, so I should start heading back.
Can you stay a bit longer?
Okay.
Sick?
Yeah, right.
I brought him a soda.
I almost got back there.
People really talk like that in real life?
It's so cute and awkward.
It's hilarious.
I need to wash my eyes out with boiling water.
Whatever, though.
At least I've got some cola now.
What the hell?
Seriously?
This is funny to you, me being in pain.
Sorry, but your face is so funny.
You know, Asuma?
You really...
You really are my classmate.
Huh?
Of course I am.
I mean, what?
We're in the same class together this year,
and we were in the same class together last year, too, right?
So...
Yeah, I mean...
We were, but...
I wanted to tell her that she's really changed somehow.
Why did I say that, stupid stupid?
Huh?
I can't move!
Why can't I move?
He paralyzed me with his cuteness!
Why can't I go back?
Free time!
I can't!
Which one should we ride first?
We gotta move fast if we want to park, Max.
Don't you have a date to go on?
Get lost.
That was blunt.
Enjoy your date, Suzuki.
If we run into you, we'll pretend you're a stranger.
Okay, you don't have to be rude about it.
They say that couples tend to argue at amusement parks,
so best of luck to you.
Thanks, Nabe. You have fun too.
If a long line makes a dude you're with get all grumpy and lame,
you should assume you're finally witnessing their true nature,
for better or for worse.
I hope that's not from experience.
Where to first?
Ooh! Let's make a stop straight ahead!
Just what we need, a popcorn bucket!
So I can walk and talk and munch all at once!
Isn't you, darling?
Darling?
If you say so.
Let's take a look at some hats, too!
Oh! They're all so adorable!
Huh?
Huh. That's a bold choice for him.
This one...seems like you.
Seems like me?
Like it'd look good on me?
A key!
In that case, let's find one that would look good on my mane!
Uh...
No, I don't need one.
Huh?
Oh!
Ah!
Yes, sir!
That was close!
The Suzuki blinders were almost engaged!
If I get too carried away, I'm gonna walk out of here looking like the rat king of crane machine prizes!
But again, I low-key wanna get at least some matching something with Tani!
Is that too much to ask?
I guess that's not really his thing.
Oh.
Hmm?
Let's get a pair.
Like we did before.
A tradition.
Yay!
So merch like this is fine, but headwear is a hard nope.
I mean, it's hard to imagine myself wearing things like that on my head.
They'd look good on you, but they'd look weird on me.
Nah, you wouldn't look weird!
Besides, in a place like this, you have to let your freak flag fly, or you'll regret it forever.
Right.
It's we've got breaking you out of that shell, little crabby crab!
Mmmmm.
Hahaha!
It's fine!
Don't force yourself on my account!
Hmmmm.
Huh?
Want some popcorn?
Voila!
Thank you.
Mmmmm.
For some reason, it really is starting to look cute to me.
What?
You didn't think I was cute before?
This day is perfecto!
Nabe and the gals made it sound like we were bound to bicker today, getting all antsy with the long wait times.
But you'd have to try not to have fun here.
It is fun.
Although, I think we're out of time to do much else.
It's already that late?
Hm?
Oh!
Asu just texted!
Aw, looks like everyone else is together!
I guess we should catch up with the party.
Boy, time sure flies when you're having fun, am I right?
Mio.
Wait.
Yusuke?
Um…
Could we… take the long way there?
Hey…
What's going on?
Today…
You've been so…
Actually yesterday too…
And before that even…
Are you gonna kill me?
What?
No…
Have I been different?
I guess…
Maybe this is me?
Maybe this is…
Take the long way there.
Hey, what's going on?
Today, you've been so...
Actually, yesterday, too.
And before that, even.
Are you gonna kill me?
What? No.
Have I been different?
I guess...
Maybe this is me getting a little weird.
What kind of laugh was that?
What is this?
Are you guys in a cult?
What's the point?
Smash brah.
All the crew members thought we looked cool.
Yeah, every employee here must have said hi to us.
Wow, Tyda.
Wow, Tyda? Screw you, man!
Then why are you only looking at me?
Hey! Let's all get a group picture for today!
Yeah!
Are you regretting not going all out and getting even weirder?
I'm not.
Okay, everyone look here!
I'm heavy a little.
Say cheese!
We'll just have to come back.
Yeah.
Yeah! Hey!
お決まりのフレーズは引き出しの中へ
何よりも振り切って声を出してみる
鏡の奥まで目を凝らして
Ah! Take the good now!
道を抜け言い合わせた影も
曇る窓へ描くように
縁取ってほしい
言葉で透き通ったり
縮む幻
差し込めた日を踏んで
跳ねた色も少しだけ好きになる
ねえ 今を隠されちゃう前に
意外な魔法をかけあって
分からなくて
分からないねって話して
音頭が触った後に見つけた
匂いが
お目を見返しとってる
お目を見返し